<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felipe Warrener-Iglesias</title>
    <link>https://felipewarrener.co.uk/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felipe Warrener-Iglesias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 23:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://felipewarrener.co.uk/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>IOLI CrackMe Challenges Walkthrough</title>
      <link>https://felipewarrener.co.uk/blog/ioli-crackmes-1-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://felipewarrener.co.uk/blog/ioli-crackmes-1-3/</guid>
      <description>This blog post is a series of write-ups for the IOLI reverse-engineering crackmes. It will end up pretty lengthy as it&amp;rsquo;s intended to be comprehensive. I will be uploading 3 solutions at a time on this blog post. You can skip to any single challenge using the following links:
Challenge 1
Challenge 2
Challenge 3
Challenge 1 This challenge consists of a simple comparison inside main() that checks if the user&amp;rsquo;s input (interpreted as a signed-integer) is equal to the value 0x149a and outputs a success message if they are equal (this can be inferred from reading the strings stored in the executable&amp;rsquo;s .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Competing in OWASP Bristol’s CTF Tournament</title>
      <link>https://felipewarrener.co.uk/blog/owasp-bristol-ctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 22:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://felipewarrener.co.uk/blog/owasp-bristol-ctf/</guid>
      <description>On Wednesday the 9th of January, I attended a CTF tournament arranged by the OWASP Bristol Chapter, SecureCodeWarrior and JustEat at the JustEat offices in London and Bristol.
I thought I’d share my experience competing in the CTF, some of the challenges and what I learnt from them. On a less important note I will also share where I finished on the tournament leaderboard!
CTF Structure As you&amp;rsquo;d guess, this CTF was based solely on web-app vulnerabilities, to be even more specific, the OWASP Top 10 vulnerabilities in web-apps.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>